<?xml version="1.0"?>
<!DOCTYPE rss SYSTEM "noticias.dtd">
<rss version="2.0">
	<channel>
		<title>Infobae</title>
		<link>https://www.infobae.com</link>
		<description>Infobae is a news website created in Argentina in 2002 by businessman Daniel Hadad. Infobae has 450 staff journalists and over a thousand stringers. Their headquarters are located in Buenos Aires. The company also has news bureaus and local editions in New York City, Mexico City, Miami, Bogotá, São Paulo and Madrid</description>
		<pubDate/>
		<webMaster/>
		<language>es-ar</language>
		<item>
			<title>El día que Maradona conquistó a Nápoles y ganó la protección de la mafia italiana</title>
			<link>https://www.infobae.com/america/deportes/2022/03/13/el-dia-que-maradona-conquisto-a-napoles-y-gano-la-proteccion-de-la-mafia-italiana/</link>
			<pubDate>13/03/22</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
	<channel>
		<title>La Nación</title>
		<link>https://www.lanacion.com.ar</link>
		<description>La Nación is an Argentine daily newspaper. As the country's leading traditional newspaper, La Nación's main competitor is the more liberal Clarín. It is regarded as a newspaper of record for Argentina. Its motto is: "La Nación will be a tribune of doctrine."</description>
		<pubDate/>
		<webMaster/>
		<language/>
		<item>
			<title>Guerra Rusia-Ucrania. Pandemia v. guerra: ¿cuál afectará más a la Argentina y la región?</title>
			<link>https://www.lanacion.com.ar/el-mundo/guerra-rusia-ucrania-pandemia-v-guerra-cual-afectara-mas-a-la-argentina-y-la-region-nid13032022/</link>
			<pubDate>13/03/22</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
	<channel>
		<title>Clarín</title>
		<link>https://www.clarin.com</link>
		<description>Clarín, is the largest newspaper in Argentina and the second most circulated in the Spanish-speaking world. It was founded by Roberto Noble in 1945, published by the Clarín Group. For many years, its director was Ernestina Herrera de Noble, the founder's wife.</description>
		<pubDate/>
		<webMaster/>
		<language/>
		<item>
			<title>Rusia bombardeó una base militar cercana a Lviv, reportan al menos 35 muertos</title>
			<link>https://www.clarin.com/mundo/rusia-bombardeo-base-cercana-lviv-cerca-frontera-polonia_0_HQG8VXZLvt.html</link>
			<pubDate>13/03/22</pubDate>
		</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

